losmovies.es 2016-11-19

# Los Movies Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

Please read the following terms and conditions carefully and pay attention to the fact that by entering this site you completely agree to its terms and conditions. This site works in accordance with copyright law. Persons who reproduce or distribute any works without a copyright owner's consent, may be in violation of this law.

#### Information Collection

When you visit LosMovies.com, we will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you choose to provide such information to us.

#### Log Files

We may automatically and through third-party tracking services (e.g., Google Analytics) gather certain non-personally identifiable information about your use of Los Movies and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamps, and related data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, solely to improve the quality of our services. Out of respect for your privacy, we do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use both session ID cookies and tracking cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to use Los Movies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use tracking cookies to better understand how you use LosMovies.com, and to enhance your user experience. A tracking cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You are free to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our offerings. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while using Los Movies.

#### Information Security

We employ encryption and other security measures to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you provide us or our partners with sensitive or confidential information, we or our partners will take commercially reasonable steps to protect such information by establishing a secure connection with your web browser, such as employing a security technology known as a secure-socket-layer ("SSL") to protect the transmission of such information. However, please be advised that while we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches from ever occurring. You transmit information to us at your own risk.

#### Your ability to edit and cancel your account

You can access "My account" section from every page on this Website to update and correct the personal details that we gathered when you subscribed and/or when you chose to use any of Los Movies's Products or Services. You must be logged in to access this information. All information is password-protected so no one can access the information but you.

If you decide to cancel your Los Movies subscription, your account will be deactivated immediately once we have received back all the discs that you have rented. However we are required to may retain your information for accounting and taxation business, operational and administrative purposes and in accordance with applicable laws.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, Los Movies will review and may edit this policy in accordance with potential changes to our business and as required by law. Los Movies reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time. This Privacy Policy may be amended in accordance with paragraph 1.2 of our Terms and Conditions (of which this Privacy Policy forms part).

If you have any questions please feel free to contact us.
